SPOOKY IN LOVE
EPISODE 10
NOVELIST YUN HAE-SEOK'S "WRITING CHAIR"
DESIGNATED
AS PRELIMINARY CULTURAL HERITAGE
URGENT: PETITION AGAINST
THE DESTRUCTION OF CHAEUM ARTRION
WE'VE SURPASSED 50,000 SIGNATURES!
REPOST: CHAEUM ARTRION
THE PRIDE OF OUR CITY
PETITION AGAINST ITS DESTRUCTION
AND CALL FOR PUBLIC DISCUSSION
IT'S ALREADY BLOWING UP ACROSS ONLINE
COMMUNITIES, THE MOMENTUM IS THERE
I DON'T KNOW IF
THEY'LL BE ABLE TO HANDLE IT
AT THIS RATE, WE CAN DEFINITELY
MAKE THIS A MAJOR PUBLIC ISSUE
I'LL REPOST THIS TOO!
PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
MOTION TO DISMISS
CEO CHEON YEO-RI
PROXY FOR GENERAL MEETING OF SHAREHOLDERS
NAME OF PROXY: HONG JI-HYO
MAY 20, 2026
SHAREHOLDER GRANTING PROXY: HAN SE-IN
IN FAVOR
OPPOSED
RESULTS OF ADVANCE ELECTRONIC VOTING
(PARTICIPATION BY
40.0% OF TOTAL SHARES)
IN FAVOR 51.0%
OPPOSED 49.0%
RESULTS OF IN-PERSON VOTING
(PARTICIPATION BY
60.0% OF TOTAL SHARES)
IN FAVOR 48.5%
OPPOSED 51.5%
FINAL AGGREGATED RESULTS
IN FAVOR 49.5%
OPPOSED 50.5%
MOTION TO DISMISS CEO CHEON YEO-RI
REJECTED
CEO CHEON YEO-RI
CEO KANG MIN-HWAN
A COASTAL RESCUE BOAT
CARRYING FOUR COAST GUARD OFFICERS
WERE THE FIRST TO ARRIVE AT THE SCENE
AND ASSESS THE SITUATION
BORN SAVAGE
ANDONG MIRAE HOSPITAL
119 PARAMEDICS
INCOMING CALL
SECRETARY EOM
102♥
SPOOKY IN LOVE
PARK SEUNG-JAE